For our fifth and final line.
You're going to connect the top of the line you just drew at the top of nail.
You'll come down at another forty five degree angle and bring another line down.
This one you can kind of bring off to the end of the nail, or you can draw another horizontal line to the middle edge of the finger, to look like you're getting ready to start another heartbeat line.
The choice is up to you, on either one that you do, but you want to do this to all ten.
Don't be worried about exactly how tall the lines go, not everyone's heartbeat is normal.
Not everyone has a strong pulse; some people have a real light one.
And, again just, you can finish it out by doing another horizontal line coming out to the right hand side of the nail.
That is how you do your fifth; it can be your fifth or your fifth and sixth line in your heart monitor line.
Once you have it done, again you'll have five or six lines total, you'll want to make sure that the polish wasn't stringy in the striping brush, if you get any on the side of the finger, you can just dip your French manicure brush back in your polish remover and just clean up the sides.
You may have a little bit of polish there, you may not.
If you do, just kind of clean it up just a little.
Making sure that there's not so much acetone that it causes the entire design to run.
Now that's how you do the heart monitor nail design.